{"test_questions": [[{"question": "ODBC minimum SQL grammar contains which of the following?", "opta": "INSERT, UPDATE, DELETE only", "optb": "Stored Procedures only", "optc": "Literals for date, time and timestamp only", "optd": "CREATE VIEW, DROP VIEW only", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using ODBC, which of the following processes ODBC requests and submits specific SQL statements to a given type of data source?", "opta": "Data source", "optb": "Driver", "optc": "Driver manager", "optd": "DBMS", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ODBC core API consists of which of the following functions?", "opta": "Commit or rollback transactions only", "optb": "Connect to data sources with driver-specific information only", "optc": "Connect to data sources only", "optd": "Both 1 and 3 above are in the OBDC core API.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ is a simple object model that is easier to understand and use than OLE DB, and is frequently used for database applications.", "opta": "ASP", "optb": "XML", "optc": "ODBC", "optd": "ADO", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ODBC core SQL grammar contains which of the following?:", "opta": "INSERT, UPDATE, DELETE only", "optb": "Stored procedures only", "optc": "Full SELECT (includes subqueries) only", "optd": "Both 1 and 3 above are contained in the ODBC core SQL.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ is considered to be one of the foundations of data access in the Microsoft world.", "opta": "ODBC", "optb": "OLE DB", "optc": "JPCD", "optd": "ADO", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ is an interface by which application programs can access and process SQL databases in a DBMS-independent manner.", "opta": "ODBC", "optb": "OLE DB", "optc": "JPCD", "optd": "ADO", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following are goals of OLE DB?", "opta": "Create object interfaces for DBMS functionality pieces only.", "optb": "Increase flexibility only.", "optc": "Object interface over any type of data only.", "optd": "All of the above as goals of OLE DB.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An ODBC data structure that identifies a database and the DBMS that processes it is called a(n):", "opta": "data source.", "optb": "driver manager.", "optc": "driver.", "optd": "API.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In OLE DB, actions that an object can perform are called:", "opta": "properties.", "optb": "collections.", "optc": "methods.", "optd": "abstractions.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In OLE DB, which of the following represents characteristics of the recordset abstraction?", "opta": "Properties", "optb": "Collections", "optc": "Methods", "optd": "Abstractions", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In ODBC, a file that can be shared among database users is called a:", "opta": "system data source.", "optb": "file data source.", "optc": "user data source.", "optd": "SQL text file.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ is an object-oriented interface that encapsulates data-server functionality.", "opta": "ODBC", "optb": "OLE DB", "optc": "JPCD", "optd": "ADO", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using ODBC, which of the following serves as an intermediary between the application and the DBMS drivers?", "opta": "Data source", "optb": "Driver", "optc": "Driver manager", "optd": "OLE DB", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ODBC Level 1 API contains which of the following functions?", "opta": "Browse possible connections and data sources only", "optb": "Connect to data sources with driver-specific information only", "optc": "Process a scrollable cursor only", "optd": "Both 1 and 3 above are in the OBDC Level 1 API.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In OLE DB, a service provider:", "opta": "does not own data only.", "optb": "transforms data through OLE DB interfaces only.", "optc": "is both a consumer and a provider of data only.", "optd": "All of the above are true of an OLE DB service provider.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In OLE DB, a tabular data provider:", "opta": "does not own data.", "optb": "transforms data through ODE DB interfaces.", "optc": "is both a consumer and a provider of data.", "optd": "exposes data via rowsets.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ODBC Level 2 API contains which the following functions?", "opta": "Commit or rollback transactions only", "optb": "Connect to data sources with driver-specific information only", "optc": "Connect to data sources only", "optd": "All of the above are contained in the OBDC Level 2 API", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In ODBC, a data source that is local to a single computer is called a:", "opta": "system data source.", "optb": "file data source.", "optc": "user data source.", "optd": "SQL text file.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ is a cover for utilizing OLE DB that is designed for use by almost any language.", "opta": "ODBC", "optb": "ASP", "optc": "JPCD", "optd": "ADO", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}